https://www.cricjharkhand.org/privacy-policy/

Home
About
President’s Message
Organization Structure
History of JSCA (BCA)
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. We respect your right to privacy and shall protect and respect the privacy of all visitors who provide personal information by filling out forms and submitting it through this web site.
Our policy is to collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit our web site unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us. However, our web servers do automatically recognize some non-personal information such as volume and timing of access as well as the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our site.
Certain personal information that you may voluntarily share with us is your e-mail address, your messages when you communicate electronically with us, information that you provide voluntarily on surveys & other forms, or when registering for personalized services. Your information is kept confidential, unaltered, and used only by us to administer your request.
Information about your visit is gathered in an aggregate manner for quality control, security, and improvement of our site.
We do not disclose or sell any personally identifiable information collected at this site to other companies or organizations. Selected information, where authorized by you, maybe published at this website or in any of our publications as information of general interest. This could be information like your name, company name, location, address, etc.
Should you feel that this Privacy Policy has been violated please contact us.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
